ALLYN CHRISTOPHER: All right, we're getting close.
It's almost a completely brand new cleaner, just some of the exterior accessories and we're going to be ready to pick some dirt up.
All right.
Oh, actually heavy leaves.
It's what it's designed for.
All right.
What I'm going to do here--this is a new float head.
New float head, the old float head had water in it, sometimes that they get all cracked.
I always like the fact that they'll get water in them and you'll splash them here and squeeze and the water doesn't come out.
I don't know how gets in and why it isn't coming out, but that's for other minds to decide.
It actually goes over here and just sits on, and as you can tell by the fact that this is augered, we're just going to spin it on.
Again, older frame, be careful, because this motion of the spinning could snap it here then you're into a whole other repair that includes glues and expoxys you've going to buy on your own, and also it's a nonsense.
I'm going to leave it just about a finger's length away from the top of the mast.
When you actually put this back in the pool and adjust and install like you did when it was new, you'll go through the process of seeing whether it's a little too way your center of floatness is in the right position.
But once it's on there, it's nice and stiff and you're good to go, that's your float head.